letmeknow.in 2015-12-29

# 

## Privacy Policy

By using our website, you consent to our privacy policy.

When you register on letmeknow.in website, we collect information from you i.e. your Name, Email, College/ Workplace details.

 **  

### How do we use your information?

**

* We use this information to enhance and personalize your experience with us, by sending you periodic updates via e-mail. You have the choice to opt out of receiving them.
* The feedback we receive from you helps us improve our website and better cater to your needs.
* We may also record anonymous visits from you and keep track of visitor activity on our website to improve our services and maintain our reach.
* We do not, at any time, trade, sell, or transfer your personal information.

You have the option of viewing our site anonymously (without registration).

**

### Third- party Links:

**

Let Me Know is a portal that helps you find various opportunities. To this end, we often include third- party links on our website. The third- party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We thus bear no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these third- party websites. We request you to exercise caution and browse the privacy policy applicable to the concerned website.   
Do refer our **_Terms of Use_**that govern your use of our website.   

**

###  How do we protect your information?

**

We have put in place a variety of security measures to ensure that your personally identifiable information is fully secure.  
**You may contact us in case of technical or general queries at[contactus@letmeknow.in](mailto:contactus@letmeknow.in) .**We would be glad to answer your queries at the earliest. 

**_The Let Me Know Team_**
